Every war has its casualties.
Hostile Territory is a western, action, drama film directed by Brian Presley.
Former P.O.W.
Jack Calgrove moves Heaven and Earth to be reunited with
his children following the Civil War.
After returning home, Jack discovers that his wife has tragically died and his children, presumed to be orphans, are
heading deep into the West on a train crossing enemy lines, with the intent of being placed into new homes.
Calgrove and another soldier team up with a troop of Native American
sharpshooters and a freed slave as they try to stop the train.
Jack Calgrove, played by Brian Presley.
Andrew Lee, played by Matt McCoy.
Frank Smith, played by Brad Leland.
Sarah, played by Brea Bee.
Daniel Glenn, played by Lew Temple.
Desmond Richards, played by Craig Tate.
Interceptor is a 2022 action thriller film directed by Matthew Reilly in his directorial
debut, from a screenplay by Reilly and Stuart Beattie and a story by Reilly.
An international co-production between Australia and the United
States, the film stars Elsa Pataky and Luke Bracey.
It follows a tough and reality-bruised army officer who finds herself in charge of a lone nuclear missile interceptor base
in the middle of the Pacific Ocean after she is wrongfully drummed out of her dream job at the Pentagon.
The film began streaming on Netflix on June 3, 2022, and climbed to number one on
the streamer's top 10 list with about 50 million hours viewed.
It received mixed reviews from critics, and was nominated for
Best Production Design at the 12th AACTA Awards.
The film explores themes of civil war, orphanage, train, orphan, post war.
The tone is emotional and thought_provoking.